Helpless Cindy thanks her savior.
Stop. This isn't right.
I need no saving.
We, women, need no saving.
You should have also depicted in this film
that women can defend themselves.
Where's the rest of the money
from the transaction in Magallanes?
That's 20 million pesos.
Do you think I forgot about it?
Wait, Congressman!
Hold on!
Why did you even accept this project?
Because I am bound by a contract.
How about you?
Why do you insist on writing a film?
To correct the mistakes I made before.
So if you're telling me
that you're trapped, Joyce...
I mean, Savana.
Let's work together to be free,
and to create a decent output.
Grandpa, how are you?
When did you get out of jail?
Liam dropped the case against me.
And he gave the residents of Verde Village
a livelihood.
My friend, as we all know,
Liam is experiencing trauma
because of the assassination attempt on him.
So I told him to take a break.
May I know how long he will be on break?
I will tell him to come back
as soon as he's okay.
In the meantime, I will manage Casa Fuerte.
Tell your son to recover quickly.
Because if not,
his break might become indefinite.
And a gentle reminder...
You are just the face of the company.
A cover-up for my money.
We know who's the brain of this company.
And that's Liam.
You and Vergil don't have that, my friend.
Make sure he'll come back
to work on my projects.
The longer it takes, the more money I lose.
You might get into debt.
You know how I collect my money.
Savana, can you say your line
on page 38, sequence 28?
I won't leave you here.
We'll get out of this cave together,
whether you like it or not.
Why are you so stubborn?
I told you to leave.
I'm not leaving because I love you!
Miss Via, I think being safe is
like living in a dangerous place.
From where we are sitting right now,
I think we're still in a safe space, right?
That's good. Pack up!
Okay, thank you, everyone.
Please assist Miss Savana.
- Thank you.
Hello.
When will you come back?
Of course, we'll have our vacation
when you come back, okay?
I'm done with work, too.
I'll let you know once I get home.
Bye.
Thank you.
Boss Bro.
Borj, wow, good job.
You came right when the look test was over.
Sorry, Boss Bro.
Ma'am Tess asked me to bring her here.
My mom?
- Where is she?
- She's in the lobby.
By the way, Borj...
You're into show business, right?
A little. Why, Boss Bro?
Do you know if Savana has a boyfriend?
People don't know anything about her
aside from her being vocal
regarding social issues.
But wait, is this still about work?
You're so silly.
- Don't make an issue out of it.
- I'm just asking.
Come on.
Let's go see my mom.
Fine.
Let's go.
Hi, Mom!
Hi, Son.
- Hi, Auntie.
- Hello.
Oh, hello.
Savana?
Savana!
Savana.
Hi!
Hello.
My name's Tess.
I am Liam's mom.
- Hi, Aunt Tess.
- Hi, Savana.
I'm your biggest fan.
I always watch your TV series,
Captive Hearts.
Mom, take it easy.
Auntie, let's go out.
Let's have dinner. It's my treat.
Dinner?
I prepared dinner at home.
- Yes.
- Oh.
Yes.
Savana, come with us.
Have dinner with us at home.
Come with us. Let's go?
Come on.
Sure.
Okay.
For real? I'm so thrilled.
Thank you, Savana.
Of course.
Good luck on your dinner date, Boss Bro.
Via, let's just have dinner at home?
Yeah, sure.
Can I bring Queenie?
Sure.
Thank you.
I only prepared dinner for three, son.
Just for three people.
But we can have some food delivered. Right?
Yeah, I'll order some food
and have it delivered.
I'll take care of it, Auntie.
- Let's go.
- I can smell trouble.
Come on, Savana.
Let's go so you can try my cooking.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Try this, Savana.
This is Liam's second favorite.
My version of kare-kare,
next to my best-seller, adobo.
I love kare-kare, too.
Oh, really? Go ahead.
Eat some more.
Lovely.
This is also your favorite, right, Miss Via?
The kare-kare?
Yes, of course.
Kare-kare is also my favorite, Auntie.
Have some more. Help yourself.
- Mom.
- Don't be shy.
That's enough. She can't eat all of that.
It's just a small serving.
- Right?
- Yes, Auntie. Just a little.
I'm on a diet, too.
Oh, dear. Forget about diet.
There's no such thing as diet,
especially when you're here.
What else do you want?
There's shrimp paste.
Here.
- Come on. Put some of this.
- Thank you.
I'm sorry.
My mom is such a big fan of yours.
I know, right?
I love your scene in Captive Hearts.
The one with Anastacia, the villain.
The scene where you said,
"I won't wait for God anymore!
I'll give you your karma!"
Is that right?
Miss Tess is not just a great cook.
She's also a good actress.
Go on, eat.
Wow, looks like she's upstaging you.
It seems that she's auditioning
for the role of daughter-in-law.
The kare-kare is good.
Thank you.
Here is some more.
Auntie, your kare-kare is really good.
What recipe do you use?
Oh, it's a family secret.
But don't worry,
I will teach you how to cook it.
Would you like that?
- Yes.
- Okay, I will.
I will share the recipe to you.
Go on and eat.
There.
Thank you, Mom.
Savana, I was surprised
that you still accepted this project.
Why not?
Well, I recall from our interview
that you have a strong conviction
against land grabbers.
Isn't it difficult to work
with people with principles
that are different from yours?
Via.
What matters is to be given a second chance
to rectify mistakes.
What do you mean?
If you are referring to Casa Fuerte,
Liam and I already talked.
I wouldn't have accepted the movie project.
If he didn't make it up
to the residents of Verde Village.
I didn't know you two were talking.
For the project, of course.
Okay.
For second chances.
That's the theme of the movie, right?
Speaking of changes...
Liam, when can we revise our script?
Do we have to do locked-in writing?
Because if we do,
I have a resort in Tagaytay.
Tagaytay?
How long will you need to be locked-in
to expedite the revision?
It depends on how fast Liam can write.
Thank you so much for your offer, Savana.
I'll ask my team.
Great.
Where's your powder room?
Over here.
Thank you. Excuse me.
Love, do you need a locked-in writing?
Well, I suppose
if we have to beat the deadline.
Is it okay with you?
Yeah.
Of course!
Don't worry about me.
Don't worry, I'm okay.
Do what you have to do.
Thank you, Via.
Auntie, let me help you wash the dishes.
Oh, you don't have to, darling.
It's okay.
Wait, this is my house.
- Let me do it.
- You're a guest.
No. Just get some rest.
Go on. Relax.
I insist, Auntie.
I want to help. I know how to wash dishes.
Really? For real?
Yes.
We didn't have a housemaid before.
So I always do the dishes.
Now I'm shy.
I'm doing the dishes with a celebrity.
I feel privileged.
Oh, no. Don't think that way.
It's not like that.
No, I got this.
- It's okay...
- I'll do it.
Let me do it, Auntie.
I'm good at washing the dishes.
No. Put it down.
You made me happy today.
Super. My heart is full of happiness.
You made me so happy, Savana.
Joyce?
What's the problem?
Nothing, Mom.
The soap got in my eyes.
Tell me the truth.
Did you and Liam fight?
Sometimes, I can't handle Liam anymore.
Mom, why is it like that?
Why is he putting his ambition first?
What about me and his son?
Aren't we part of his dreams?
I understand what you feel, my child.
But sometimes, you just have to remind Liam
the reason why he's doing things.
Joyce, my dear.
Please, don't give up on Liam. Okay?
Auntie.
Liam! Liam, your mom!
- Mom.
- Liam!
- Auntie, are you okay?
Mom, what's wrong?
Borj, please call an ambulance.
Oh my God! What happened?
- Savana!
- I don't know.
We were just washing the dishes
when she got dizzy.
Mom, are you okay?
Get me some water, please. I'm okay.
I'm fine. I just got dizzy.
Are you sure? I'm afraid it's...
No, son.
No. Don't overreact. I just got dizzy.
I just got excited.
I was just so excited to be with Savana.
- Are you sure?
- Auntie...
Yes.
Get some rest for now. We'll do the cleaning.
No, no. That would be embarrassing.
- I'm okay.
- Auntie, do you want to get some fresh air?
I'll go with you.
Okay.
Okay, let's go.
Savana, why did you order our caretaker
to prepare the resort in Tagaytay?
Savana, I'll just bring your stuff
to your room.
Excuse me, Madam.
Yes, Mommy.
We need it for our locked-in writing
at Blacksmith.
Is Liam going to join?
Is he coming?
Yes, because he's the creative manager.
Tell Liam that he's very much welcome
at our resort.
I will have the biggest suite
ready for the two of you.
What?
You didn't tell me Liam made headlines
because he's an heir
of the Herrera Group of Companies.
I didn't know he was rich.
And so what, Mom?
You should get close to him.
Work on it.
That's what I mean.
You are unbelievable, Mom.
Mom, you're hurting me!
Let's make it clear.
Why did you accept such a cheap movie
if you're not interested in Liam?
You have a lot of better offers.
What do you take me for, Mom?
A product that you can sell to just anyone?
I'm doing the project in Blacksmith
because they listen to me
instead of controlling me.
What are you trying to say?
That I am controlling you?
Is that what you mean? Is that it?
I worked hard for your career.
I won't let you ruin it!
And I won't let us go back to being poor.
My mom is the worst.
I did everything she wanted.
I always do what she wants.
Everything.
Everything she wants.
But why can't she give me a little space?
- Savana...
- Even just a little respect.
Savana, that's enough. You're already drunk.
- You should stop.
- I'm not drunk yet.
You're not drunk yet, too.
- Savana, that's enough.
- Let's drink some more.
Cheers!
Savana, you've had enough.
No.
Cheers, Tristan. Join me.
I need to drink.
Please? Cheers.
That's enough, Savana.
You know what...
People think that life is all good
when you're a celebrity.
But no!
They don't know about the pressure.
Okay. Let's go. That's enough.
I'll drive you home.
- Let's go.
- No.
- I don't want to go home yet.
- Savana, stop.
- Tonight...
- Savana, that's enough.
I'll have fun tonight.
Because it's the first time
that I get to go out.
Savana, enough.
Let's go. I'll drive you home.
- Come on.
- I said no!
Savana, that's enough!
Savana!
- Waiter, one more round, please.
- What's going on?
Maxine.
Savana's drunk already.
She doesn't want to go home.
- I have an early call time tomorrow.
- Do you have to go?
Go. We'll take care of Savana.
Thank you, Maxine. I owe you one.
- Please take care of Savana.
- Sure.
- Savana.
- Take care.
Hi, girls!
Via, do we have a problem?
Is there something I should be worried about?
What is this about?
Is this about the unexpected dinner with Mom?
Via, I'm sorry. I'll make it up to you.
That's where you're good at.
Second chances.
Are you jealous of Savana?
Why didn't you tell me
you're in constant communication with her?
Via, she's my actor. We're making a film.
I thought you understood.
Via, I need to save this project.
I need to appease her.
I'm sorry.
Maybe I just have a lot on my mind.
It's okay, Love.
I'm sorry, too.
I love you.
Girls, let's dance.
Chanel, take a video.
You know what, guys...
My mom is like this.
Savana...
Savana, act more convincingly.
Savana, you're overacting.
Savana, you should cry!
Savana.
Savana, you should only
shed tears in your left eye.
Savana, wait!
Don't eat that, Savana!
You're so fat already!
This is so hard.
I can't make decisions for myself!
I don't want this anymore.
Our friend gets drunk so easily.
Really, Savana?
Who's so controlling?
- Who's controlling?
- Who else?
My mom is controlling.
She's a terror manager.
- OMG, girls. This is so juicy.
- I'm getting tired of it.
Just continue recording it.
I can't make decisions for myself!
Our friend can't handle alcohol.
Really, Savana?
Who's so controlling?
Who's controlling?
Who else?
My mom, who's a terror manager...
She is so controlling.
Are you recording this?
Make sure you're doing it right.
I'm like...
I'm like a goldfish.
I'm like a goldfish. Like...
Can you imagine a goldfish?
Goldfish.
I'm like a goldfish in a very tiny aquarium.
What does a goldfish look like again?
- So that's what a goldfish looks like.
- That's a goldfish.
Why won't she just flush me in the toilet?
It's so messy. Sorry.
Yeah.
Are you okay?
Yes.
I'm okay.
What the heck!
Are you really throwing up here?
I was just kidding. I'm still okay.
Look, I can still dance.
I don't want to go home yet.
- Party, party!
- Come on, Savana!
Let's go.
I don't want to go home yet.
Let's go back.
- Let's go back!
- No!
I'm not enjoying it anymore, so let's go.
Maxine, I'm still having a good time.
I'm still having fun, so let's go.
- Let's go back.
- She's so hopeless.
What do we do?
Are we going to leave Savana here?
- She asked for it.
- Are you sure?
You can stay with her if you want.
Stay with her.
No, let's go.
Come on, let's go.
Hey!
Isn't she a celebrity?
Come on, bro.
That's Savana.
Savana?
Savana!
- Who are you...
- Want to come with us?
Why are you grabbing me?
- Let's have fun.
- Let go of me!
- Join us.
- Let go...
How dare you!
Get her!
Help!
Come with us!
Let go of me!
Help me, please!
Help me!
Help!
- Love!
- Savana!
- Liam!
- Leave her alone!
Love...
Oh my God, Savana.
Savana!
Get in! Get in the car.
Hey!
Love...
- Are you guys okay?
- Liam.
Who are they?
- Careful with her head.
- Yeah.
I'll get some cold water and a towel.
Okay.
Joyce...
What were you doing?
Why are you getting drunk?
When we were still together
back in the old world,
you didn't even take a sip of alcohol.
I want you to meet Liam, my boyfriend.
Liam Herrera.
You know each other?
He was at my filming the other day.
You didn't tell me that you know each other.
Auntie, your kare-kare is so good.
What recipe do you use?
Oh, it's a family secret.
But don't worry.
I'll share my recipe with you, Savana.
Would you like that?
- Yes, sure.
- Okay, I will.
I will give you the recipe.
Love...
Can you give us some privacy for now?
I'll just give Savana a sponge bath.
Sure.
I won't leave you here.
We'll get out of this cave together,
whether you like it or not.
Why are you so stubborn?
I said, go.
I'm not going anywhere because I love you!
I saw the way you look at her.
What do you mean?
Liam, I'm a woman, too.
I know how a man looks at me
when he likes me.
Are you jealous of Savana?
Please...
Forget about whatever you are feeling
right now.
I will also pretend
that this conversation never happened.
I love you.
I love you so much.
Sorry.
Breakfast?
How are you feeling?
Are you okay now?
Have some coffee...
To cure your hangover.
Sorry, why are you here?
This is my condo.
Sorry, don't you remember anything
about what happened?
You almost got yourself in danger, Savana.
Good thing Liam and I passed by.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Please tell Liam, I'm sorry.
This is so embarrassing.
Oh, dear. Sorry.
Please tell him I'm sorry.
This really is embarrassing.
- I'm so sorry.
- It's okay. Don't worry about it.
Savana, if you need someone to talk to...
I'm here, okay?
I'm sure I'm better company than alcohol.
I'll leave you for now.
Go, eat.
I should leave.
Go on, eat breakfast first.
I'll give you your privacy. Go ahead.
I'm like a goldfish.
She's so controlling.
My mom, who's a terror manager,
is so controlling.
What is this, Savana?
What kind of life choices
have you been making?
What am I doing to myself?
[A Thousand Miles Skin Care]
It's too early in the day to be frowning.
That's bad luck.
Do you want to eat?
Yes.
Okay. Then, let's go.
Bro, I'm just curious.
You are either mad or lonely
whenever you pass by this place.
Is it because of that billboard?
There are things in the past
that I want to change.
Decisions I made
that I should have thought about
more carefully.
If only I knew the repercussions...
Bro! You're still in control of your life.
You can't bring back the past,
but you can make the right choices
for the people you love.
What if I want to bring back
the people whom I lost?
Have you asked yourself
if they want to be back in your life?
- That's some serious talk.
- Yes... Real talk, bro.
Do you know why you're having a hard time?
Why?
You can't stand by what makes you happy.
Girl, you're driving me nuts.
You didn't come home last night.
I stayed up late waiting for you.
But don't worry, I took care of your mom.
We look like each other, anyway.
I will just send your stuff to the resort.
Be safe. Take care, okay?
Bye.
- Smile!
- Picture, picture!
- Guys, selfie!
- Wacky!
They won't stop taking pictures.
I know.
Doesn't she have a road manager?
Let her be. She likes it.
Welcome to our resort.
OMG! The food is overflowing!
We're going to eat.
We're going to swim.
- Swim?
- Just give me time.
- Are we on vacation?
- Yes, Borj.
Are we here to work or to have fun??
Why, Liam?
Are we going straight to work?
Okay, fine.
You can swim.
- Let's go!
- Come on, hurry up!
- You're too excited.
- Be careful.
Oh, wow.
He came prepared.
He really came prepared.
Hey!
- Come on!
- Later. I still have to work.
It's cold.
Go, Deedee!
What?
Go, fight!
All right!
Get your drinks.
Can you please hand me that?
Go ahead.
Can I have some grapes?
That's good.
This one... Try this one.
Yeah, this is good.
The action scenes won't be a problem.
A reluctant hero who got branded
as a traitor by the community
because of a single mistake.
- But...
- The hero's objective
is to make up for the wrong
he did to the woman he loves.
He can't tell her that it was his fault
that her family died.
So, should the movie end with their breakup?
It's enough that he paid for his sins
by saving the whole community.
But he doesn't get the girl in the end.
If you were to ask me, the hero should die.
That's his biggest redemption.
Sacrificing his life.
That's me. Why would you kill me?
That will make you a hero.
It's morbid, though.
And then maybe they can be reincarnated.
They will meet at a different time.
Deedee,
I think that's a different film already.
What do you think, Boss Bro?
I think they should end up together.
Right. A happy ending.
Like how, Liam?
He will confess to her everything.
He'll pay for his sins.
He'll take in all of the woman's anger.
But in the process,
the girl will see
how much effort the man puts
into changing his ways.
After all,
that's what our movie is all about.
It's about second chances.
Excuse me. I have to take this call.
Hello?
Oh my, a crocodile!
Sorry, Savana.
Liam.
I'm sorry, Savana.
I went swimming
so I won't have to swim with the others.
Actually, that's what I have in mind, too.
Savana, if you don't mind...
What really happened?
Why did you get drunk the other night?
Sorry if I have invaded your privacy...
It's okay.
You have the right to ask.
You saved me.
Don't worry about that.
I don't know, Liam.
I know I wanted this.
Many will do everything
to get to where I am right now.
But I feel like I'm a robot.
A robot that is being controlled.
"Savana, do this."
"Act like this... Cry like that."
"You can't make a mistake!"
You're brave.
Why are you letting them control you?
What made you say that I'm brave?
You defended the residents of Verde Village
from me, remember?
Why can't you defend yourself?
Maybe that's how I deal
with all my anger towards this world...
Through my advocacies.
Savana...
I hope you use the bravery you've shown me
to fight for your own happiness.
I still need to muster enough courage.
Via.
I was about to text you
that this is my mom's treat.
Don't worry. I can deal with your mom.
He's the reason why my dreams for you
got ruined.
Everything that has happened to us
is because of our choices.
Joyce...
Joyce.
- We should kill the hero.
- Right. Because he's a traitor.
Disloyal and unfaithful.
Even I could kill that man.
Actually, he and his mistress.
This story should have a magical typewriter.
Savana! I said this story should have magic.
They got separated
because of that magical typewriter.
Maybe her non-showbiz boyfriend.